Resume

Mohit Thakre

223 Subhas Apt Goyal Nagar, Near Bengali square Indore,

Mobile No-+91 9584180144

E-mail- mohit.thakre27@gmail.com

Career Objective

To build my career in progressive organization, that will provide me executing opportunities to learn more and utilize my skills and experience. My key strength is hard working and ability to learn more and produce result with in a reduced time farm and with minimum learning curve...

Work Experience

R. k. Electrical (Electrical Contractor) Indore.

April 2016 TO Present

Job work:-Electrical site project Supervision and Execution i.e,

- Work for Roof top solar system, solar pump, solar Street light, solar heater.
- Supervision on Electrification work.
- Execute work for final billing.
- Work on LRP Project, and R-APDRP Project, Pole errection work, Ab cabling for reduces losess.

Essel Vidyut Vitran (Ujjain) Pvt. Ltd. (MPPKVVCL Distribution Franchise)

November 2014 to February 2016

As a field executive Engineer

Job Profile

- Arrangement of 33 KV, 11KV shut down as per requirement.
- Planning for PTDB installation, MMR & A.B cabling for reduce T&C losses.
- Consumer indexing for centralize the consumer in billing data base.
- Survey of LT and HT line for preparing the proposal & Estimate.
- Supervision of executing work.
- Street light connection shifting work on AB cable and New switching point installation work according to the load and cable's capacity
- Joint measurement of executed work for final billing.

Execution work: - Pole erection, AB cabling, PTDB installation, DTR metering, Consumer shifting, Conductor & Pole Dismantling and **Quality Check** also for the same.

Baba Communication Pvt. Ltd. (Nagpur)

June 2013 to July 2014

As a field executive Engineer

JOB PROFILE: -

- Project Supervision on executing work
- Meter replacement work
- DT Sanitizations Project work,
- Team work in Electrical Site.
- Joint measurement of executed work for final billing.

Execution work:-DTR metering replacement, Feeder survey in lt line, Supervision on project work.

Academic Qualification

Examination	Institution	Board / University	Year	Aggregate
B.E.(EC)	Malwa Institute of Technology Indore	R.G.P.V. Bhopal	2013	67.4%
H.S.S.C.E.	Govt. Excellence Higher Secondary School Katangi	Board of Secondary Education , M.P.	2009	68.8%
H.S.C.E.	Govt. Excellence Higher Secondary School Katangi	Board of Secondary Education , M.P.	2007	76.6%

Technical Skills

• **Software's :** C-C++, MS Office

• Operating system: Windows XP, Windows 7, Windows 8,8.1, 10.

Projects Undertaken

• Major Project: Microcontroller Based Home Automation & security system with GSM Module.

• **Minor Project:** Function Generator.

Indusrial Training

• Duration : 30 days

• Object : All India Radio Station

• Training center: Balaghat (M.P.)

Personal Information

Name : Mohit Thakre Date : 27-12-1991

Father's name : Mr. Ishwar Dayal Thakre

Languages Known : Hindi, English Marital Status : Unmarried

Permanent Address : Ward No 4, Near Govt Hosp Katangi,

Dist Balaghat, (M.P).

Mobile No. : +91-9584180144

Hobbies : Playing Cricket, Listening Music

Strengths : Leadership, Dedicated to work, Honesty, Team Cordination,

Declaration

I do hear by declare that the particulars of information and facts stated hear in above are true, correct and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date:-.... Mohit Thakre

